INGLORIOM
Why are you still fighting
while lost in the depths of my mind?
We are one, Yugo.
Think before it's too late.
I'm disappointed, Dally, I thought you...
I will never be anything like you!
You... give me back my son, right now!
Something bad is happening out there.
If anything I'm...
Will you calm down, you little beast?
No way.
So, you're back from vacation?
Yeah, you could say that.
I saw what he did to you. I'm sorry.
-It wasn't your fault, buddy.
-Of course it's his fault. He created me.
If Yugo hadn't played god, I wouldn't be
here, beating the life out of you.
You! I'm going to free you, but I promise
it's not going to be for the joy of it.
And when this is over, we are going
to have a little talk about all this.
If we get out of this alive, we can have
as many talks as you want, Goultard.
You understand that by talk
I meant fight, revenge
and having my fist
in your nasty dragon face, right?
Yes, I did understand that...
Stop it! You're too weak
to handle these powers.
Thank you.
-I didn't do it for you.
-I know, but, thanks all the same.
Adamai! Nice to see you again, brother.
-Oropo!
-My little brother.
Now it's time to get
this family party started.
Adamai, my intentions haven't changed.
I want to make a better world,
to replace those who rule us
but don't care about us.
You know it's Yugo's fault that I'm here.
He's the one who made me what I am,
a soulless being.
You want to make all the gods disappear,
destroy a world. How could you?
Every evolution requires sacrifice.
I hope you got stronger
while you were away.
More than you I bet.
Plus, I didn't forget to grow up.
That was a cheap shot. I need to touch
the Eliacube. Can you distract him?
I beg you not to do anything stupid.
Just let me finish this.
You'll see, one day,
we'll look back on this and smile.
How could I have been so blind?
How's this for a diversion, Yugo?
You're going to regret this.
This should help
make everything right again.
You think?
I've been controlling this power
much longer than you have.
It's true you've already practiced
a little on Ogrest and Nox,
but don't forget
I am a more experienced version of you.
-How could you win?
-Because I'm younger and faster!
I missed some things.
Are you a good guy again?
I always was.
I told you, I am you, only better!
How you think--
How you fight...
I can see you coming from a mile away.
Mama!
They... They were just born.
They shouldn't be able to walk.
No, he shouldn't be able to...
Sipho! That coward.
He's just trying to slow us down.
Don't tell me his first fight
is at this age. It's impossible.
It's possible, but I wish it wasn't.
It's okay, Mama, I've got him.
I recognize his fighting style already.
The more I know you,
the better I understand
why Oropo wants your children
to be the new gods.
The more I know you, the more
I want to knock you senseless.
Listen, I don't want to hurt any of you.
But I was given orders to keep you here.
It was for your own safety.
Can I hit him, Mama?
Say yes, please, please, please!
Okay, but play nice with your brother.
No arguing.
But Papa doesn't like it
when two fight against one.
-It's that or nothing.
-Okay, big bro, let's do it.
How are we going to do it?
Mm. The broken-nose technique!
I'm not sure that's the kind of behavior
you want to teach
your children, Evangelyne.
Perhaps, but it's not up to you.
All we needed was another fighter
in the family.
-I hit him before you did.
-Doesn't count. You hit like a princess.
-Yes, it counts!
-You couldn't knock him out on your own!
You couldn't even hit him on your own!
Echo!
Coward! Well done, big bro.
Well done, little sis!
Okay, children, time to find your father.
You argue a lot, but when
you work together, you work wonders.
No, no, not now!
I'm slowly starting to fade.
My days here are numbered.
Without the Eliacube to keep me alive,
I'd have already disappeared long ago.
Don't realize what you did to us, Yugo,
when you played god? It's all your fault!
We all have a dark side, but the strength
of a real hero is not giving in to it.
For doing horrible things, your excuse
was you were a version of Yugo.
All you did was find someone
to blame for all your destruction.
You're nothing like Yugo
and never will be!
Despite the mistakes he's made, he'd
rather sacrifice himself than hurt others.
Keep your illusions.
You're never going to change my mind!
Don't tell me I missed the final battle!
Oh, no, I didn't. Whew!
Just a few more seconds. You won't
lead me away from my chosen path.
He'll enter the portal and close it off.
Yugo, we need a solution quickly.
We're stuck
and the Eliacube is about to explode.
If Oropo leaves,
he'll destroy Ingloriom and the gods.
If we keep him here, this dimension
will disappear with us in it.
Wow! That looks super handy! Rubi?
-What? You want a pair, too?
-You can do that?
Like this?
How cool, you outdid yourself
with these! Thank you, Rubi!
Okay, this is going
to take some getting used to.
-Papa!
-Awesome wings, Papa!
They are, aren't they?
Very nice,
but no bringing them into the house.
Right, time to stop thinking
and start doing!
All this power! I can do anything!
I'm invincible!
We can't let him reach the portal!
My dear brother,
without the six Dofus giving you a boost,
you're not exactly up to par.
No... Not my friends!
Mishell.
I've always been on your side, Oropo,
but you've gone too far.
-Get him away from the portal!
-There's no way we can let you leave.
I know. But I also know
that none of you are able to stop me.
It'll all be over soon.
There is one solution.
I think I know what you're planning
and I won't leave you here alone.
I won't be alone, Sipho.
No! Don't do that to me, mistress!
Are you insane?
You sent them to Ingloriom!
I foiled your plans, darling.
Whatever you decide, it's over.
If you jump into that Zaap and set off
the Eliabomb, there'll be no gods left.
Neither old gods nor our children,
who were to replace them.
Traitor! How could you do that to me?
I could ask you the same thing.
I did all this
to make the world a better place.
You took a huge risk, Echo.
That's what I was planning on.
I was really trying to do good.
I wish it could end differently.
I know.